best-mobile-contracts.co.uk 2008-09-16

# Best Mobile Contracts - Privacy Policy

**Purposes for which we use information about you**

We may use your personal information for the following purposes: 

(a) to enable you to access and use the Services;   
(b) and/or to personalise aspects of our overall service to you;   
(c) and/or to communicate with you;   
(d) and/or to process a transaction between you and a third party 

**Passing on information about you**

Please be aware that once you use our website or our Services, you will be regarded as having given your consent to us disclosing your personal information to the following parties: 

(a) third party providers whose products or services are listed on the results pages of the channels on our website, for the purposes of obtaining an online quotation for you or comparing different products and services as requested by you;   
(b) other third parties either where necessary for those third parties to provide additional products or services requested by you or with your prior consent. 

Please also be aware that if you click the "I accept" button on the registration page of the account aggregation service or on a product aggregation page, you will be regarded as having given your consent to us providing you with information, offers and services that may be of interest to you. For example, we may e-mail you letting you know how you could save money by switching the products or services you use. 

If you click the "I accept" button on the registration page of the account aggregation service or on a product aggregation page, you will also be regarded as having given your consent to us disclosing your personal information to the following parties who may also provide you with information, offers and services: 

other companies and websites in the Best Mobile Contracts group our trusted business partners - For a current list of our trusted business partners, please email us.   
You can ask us to stop passing your information to third parties for marketing purposes at any time, which we will do. Such a request may result in us ceasing to offer the Services to you. 

We may disclose information about you in connection with legal proceedings or potential legal proceedings or if otherwise permitted to do so by law.   
**  
Third party providers and data privacy**

If you decide to enter into a contract with a third party provider through a channel on our website, the information you have provided to us together with any further information requested by, and supplied by you to, the third party provider will be held by the provider for the purposes set out in that provider's privacy policy. Therefore, you are strongly advised to read your chosen provider's privacy policy and satisfy yourself as to the purposes for which the provider will use your personal information before entering into the contract. We have no responsibility for the uses to which a provider puts your personal information once you have contracted with that provider. 

**Cookies**

A cookie is a very small text file placed on your computer by a web browser, which has been sent by a web server. It is essentially an "identification card" relating to you. The main purpose of our cookies is to identify you when you visit our website. Each time your browser requests a web page from our server, the browser sends the information in the text file back to the server and lets the server know that you have returned to that web page. We use cookies to provide you with a better service tailored to suit you. We will store your cookies for a maximum of three months. 

Cookies help you to save time. For example, if you register for our Services, a cookie helps us to remember who you are and what your preferences are. Next time you return, we can fill in any questions that you have already answered. The more you tell us about yourself, the more we can help to find information or products you want. 

If you do not accept incoming cookies then the performance of our website on your system will not be to full standard or our website may not serve at all. 

**Your Rights**

You have certain rights under the Data Protection Act 1998. For example, we will always let you have a copy of all personal information we have about you should you request it. We may charge you a fee for a copy of such information.
